CARD KINGDOM PRIVACY POLICY
===========================

**Last Updated: \[February 2024\]**

    * [Information We Collect Automatically When You Interact with Us](#_Toc152757239)

INTRODUCTION
------------

This Privacy Policy explains how Card Kingdom, Inc. (“Card Kingdom,” “we,” or “us”) collects, uses, and discloses information about you. This Privacy Policy applies when you use our websites and other online products and services (collectively, our “Website”), shop, utilize the services, or otherwise visit one of our Mox Boarding House locations, contact our customer support team, or otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our website or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
-------------------------

Information You Provide to Us
-----------------------------

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, you share information directly with us when you create an account, fill out a form or survey, apply to write for our Card Kingdom blog, make a purchase, make a sale, communicate with us via third-party platforms, participate in a contest or promotion, request customer support, sign up for our newsletter, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of personal information we may collect include your name, age, gender, email address, postal address, phone number, social media usernames, account password, credit card and other payment information including billing address, and any other information you choose to provide.

Information We Collect Automatically When You Interact with Us
--------------------------------------------------------------

When you access or use our Website or otherwise transact business with us, including by using our products and services, we automatically collect certain information, including:

* **Transactional Information:** When you make a purchase, sale to us, or return, or interact with our customer support, we collect information about the transaction, such as purchase details, purchase price, order history, customer support ticket history, and the date and location of the transaction.
* **Device and Usage Information:** We collect information about how you access our Website, including data about the device and network you use, such as your hardware model, operating system version, mobile network, IP address, unique device identifiers, and browser type. We also collect information about your activity on our Website, such as auth token (if you login to your account through a third-party), tracking ID, access times, pages and products viewed, time spent viewing such pages and products, items added to your shopping cart, links clicked, and the page you visited before navigating to our Website. When you visit one of our physical locations, we may also collect information about the device you have with you, including cellular MAC addresses.
* **Location Information:** We may approximate your location from your IP address.
* **Information Collected by Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies:** We (and our service providers) use tracking technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect information about you. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Website, services, and your experience, see which areas and features of our Website and stores are popular, and count visits. Web beacons (also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) are electronic images that we use on our Website and in our emails to help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, please see the \[[Your Rights](#_YOUR_RIGHTS)\] section below.

In addition, at our Mox locations:

* **Video Footage**: When you visit one of our stores or Mox Boarding House locations, we may collect video footage of you using closed-circuit security cameras.

Information We Collect from Other Sources
-----------------------------------------

We obtain information from third-party sources. For example, we may collect information about you from advertising networks, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social networks, our business partners, and mailing list providers.

Information We Derive
---------------------

We may derive information or draw inferences about you based on the information we collect. For example, we may make inferences about your location based on your IP address or infer that you are looking to purchase certain products or services based on your location, demographic, browsing behavior and past purchases.

USE OF INFORMATION
------------------

We use the information we collect to deliver the products and services you request and customize your experience with us. We also use the information we collect to:

* Provide, maintain, and improve our products and services;
* Process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations, receipts, invoices, customer experience surveys, and recall notices;
* Personalize and improve your experience on our Website or when you otherwise interact with us;
    
* Send you technical notices, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
* Allow you to reserve private rooms at our Mox Boarding House locations;
* Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer support;
    
* Communicate with you about products, services, and events offered by Card Kingdom and others and provide news and information that we think will interest you (see the \[[Your Rights](#_YOUR_RIGHTS)\]section below for information about how to opt out of these communications at any time);
* Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Website, products, and services;
* Personalize the advertisements you see on third-party platforms and websites (for more information, see the \[[Advertising and Analytics](#_ADVERTISING_AND_ANALYTICS)\] section below);
* Personalize the advertisements you see when you use our Website based on information provided by our advertising partners;
* Facilitate contests, sweepstakes, and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
* Detect, investigate, and prevent security incidents and other malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity and protect the rights and property of Card Kingdom and others;
* Debug to identify and repair errors in our services and Website;
* Fulfill the terms of any written agreement we have with you; and
* Comply with our legal and financial obligations.

SHARING OF INFORMATION
----------------------

We share personal information in the following circumstances or as otherwise described in this policy:

* We share personal information with vendors, service providers, and consultants that need access to personal information in order to perform services for us, such as companies that assist us with web hosting, shipping and delivery, payment processing, fraud prevention, customer support, event hosting, troubleshooting and website maintenance, and marketing and advertising.
* We may disclose personal information if we believe that disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
* We may disclose personal information, in accordance with, or required by, any insurance provider, claim evaluator, or appraiser.
* We may share personal information if we believe that your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, if we believe that you have violated the law, or if we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of Card Kingdom, our users, the public,the intellectual property of Wizards of the Coast, or others.
* We share personal information with our lawyers and other professional advisors where necessary to obtain advice or otherwise protect and manage our business interests.
* We may share personal information in connection with, or during negotiations concerning, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company.
* We share personal information with your consent or at your direction.
* We also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

ADVERTISING AND ANALYTICS
-------------------------

We allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the web. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers, and other technologies to collect information about your use of our products, services, Website, and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversion information. This information may be used by Card Kingdom and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Website and other websites, and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) or, if you are in the EU, [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

We also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of customized campaigns on third-party platforms (such as Facebook and Instagram). As part of these ad campaigns, we or the third-party platforms may convert information about you, such as your email address and phone number, into a unique value that can be matched with a user account on these platforms to allow us to learn about your interests and serve you advertising that is customized to your interests. Note that the third-party platforms

YOUR RIGHTS
-----------

Account Information
-------------------

You may request an update or correction of certain account information at any time by emailing us at [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com). If you wish to delete your account, please also email us at [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com) with your deletion request, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for our legitimate business purposes.

Cookies
-------

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually adjust your browser settings to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that removing or rejecting cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our Website.

Communications Preferences
--------------------------

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Card Kingdom by following the instructions in those communications. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account, orders, or our ongoing business relations.

Links to Other Websites and Services
------------------------------------

Card Kingdom is not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Services, including the information or content contained in such websites or services, and this Policy does not apply to them. We provide links to products available on third-party websites for your convenience. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on or to our Services, are subject to that third party’s own rules and privacy policies. Please read the terms of such websites and applications carefully and exercise care when providing your personal information.

Data Transfers
--------------

Card Kingdom is headquartered in the United States, and we have operations and service providers in the United States and other countries. Therefore, we and our service providers may transfer your personal information to, or store or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide levels of data protection that are equivalent to those of your home jurisdiction. We will take steps to ensure that your personal information receives an adequate level of protection in the jurisdictions in which we process it. If you are in the European Economic Area, we provide adequate protection for the transfer of personal data to countries outside of the EEA through a series of intercompany agreements based on the Standard Contractual Clauses authorized under EU law. You are entitled to obtain a copy of these agreements by contacting us using the contact information below. See the \[[Additional Disclosures for Individuals in Europe](#_ADDITIONAL_DISCLOSURES_FOR)\].

JURISDICTION SPECIFIC DISCLOSURES
---------------------------------

Additional Disclosures for Individuals in Europe
------------------------------------------------

If you are in the European Union (EU), European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data, and this section applies to you.

### Legal Basis for Processing

When we process your personal data, we will do so in reliance on the following lawful bases:

To perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the products and services you requested).

When we have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data to operate our business or protect our interests (e.g., to provide, maintain, and improve our products and services, conduct data analytics, and communicate with you).

To comply with our legal obligations (e.g., to maintain a record of your consents and track those who have opted out of marketing communications).

When we have your consent to do so (e.g., when you opt in to receive marketing communications from us). When consent is the legal basis for our processing your personal data, you may withdraw such consent at any time.

### Data Retention

We store other personal data to carry out the purposes for which we originally collected it and for other legitimate business purposes, including to meet our legal, regulatory, or other compliance obligations.

### Data Subject Requests

Subject to certain limitations, you have the right to request access to the personal data we hold about you and to receive your data in a portable format, the right to ask that your personal data be corrected or erased, and the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please email us at [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com).

### Questions or Complaints

If you have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Authority where you reside. Contact details for your Data Protection Authority can be found using the links below:

For individuals in the EU and EEA: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)

For individuals in the UK: [https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)

For individuals in Switzerland: [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact.html)

Additional U.S. State Disclosures
---------------------------------

The following table provides additional information about the categories of personal information we collect and how we disclose that information. You can read more about the personal information we collect in \[[information we collect](#_Information_We_Collect)\] above, how we use personal Information in \[[use of information](#_USE_OF_INFORMATION)\] above, and how we retain personal information in \[[Data Retention](#_Data_Retention)\] above.

In the preceding 12 months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for business purposes to the following categories of recipients:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **_Category of Personal Information_** | **_Categories of Recipients_** |
| Identifiers, such as your name, contact details, IP address, and other device identifiers | Vendors, service providers, partners, professional consultants, and (when necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of Card Kingdom or the public) government entities. |
| Personal information, such as your account login credentials and payment card information | Vendors, service providers, and professional consultants. |
| Characteristics of protected classifications under Federal law | Vendors, service providers, and professional consultants. |
| Commercial Information, such as your transaction history | Vendors, service providers, and professional consultants. |
| Network Activity Information, such as Content and how you interact with our Services | Vendors, service providers, partners, and professional consultants. |
| Inferences such as location, demographic, or browsing behavior | Vendors, service providers, and professional consultants. |

### Your Privacy Rights

To the extent provided for by local law and subject to applicable exceptions, individuals may have the following privacy rights in relation to their personal information:

* The right to know information about our processing of your personal information, including the specific pieces of personal information that we have collected from you;
* The right to request deletion of your personal information;
* The right to correct your personal information; and
* The right to be free from discrimination relating to the exercise of any of your privacy rights.

### Selling PersonalInformation

We don’t “sell” personal information or “share” personal information for cross-contextual behavioral advertising (as those terms are defined under applicable local law). We also don’t process sensitive personal information for the purposes of inferring characteristics about a consumer.

### Exercising Your Rights

To the extent applicable under local law, you can exercise privacy rights described in this section by submitting a request through [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com).

### Verification

In order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, change, or deletion, we may require you to verify your credentials before you can submit a request to know, correct, or delete personal information. If you do not have an account with us, or if we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity, we may ask you to provide additional personal information and proof of residency for verification. If we cannot verify your identity, we will not be able to honor your request.

### Authorized Agents

You may also submit a rights request through an authorized agent. If you do so, the agent must present signed written permission to act on your behalf and you may also be required to independently verify your identity and submit proof of your residency with us. Authorized agent requests can be submitted to [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com).

### Appeals

Depending on where you live, you may have the right to appeal a decision we make relating to requests to exercise your rights under applicable local law. To appeal a decision, please send your request to [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com).

CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
-------------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. The most current version will always be available on our website, and the effective date will be updated accordingly.

CONTACT US
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@cardkingdom.com](mailto:support@cardkingdom.com).
